freehostingcloud.com 2013-06-03

# FreeHostingCloud

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected on the FreeHostingCloud.com website, or submitted to FreeHostingCloud.com at any time through any of our services on the website. Personally Identifiable Information - When visiting FreeHostingCloud.com`s Web site and signing-up for or using an FreeHostingCloud.com powered service such as registering for a domain, our Forum, Tell-A-Friend or Reporting Abuse, you may choose to supply FreeHostingCloud.com with information that identifies you personally. This information may include your name and contact information, as well as other demographic or commerce related information. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a users computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browsers “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you dont have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but you will be asked to enter your username and password again every time you closed your browser or your session has timed out. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers.” This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by FreeHostingCloud.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to prevent and block abusers to keep using our services such as members who violates our terms of service. We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate of usage and volume statistics to determine how our users navigate through our website and to know how many users are using our services demographically. 

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which it is intended. This may include administering a service such as registration, email, forum, etc., or contacting you if you have indicated your permission to do so by agreeing to accept further notification and service announcement from us on your member profile page. You can choose to opt-out of receiving any further notification from your member profile page. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission. 

**Support Forum**

If you use the Support Forum on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in this forum. 

**Internal Surveys**

Upon using our free services, you will be requested to participate in our periodic internal surveys which are conducted by FreeHostingCloud.com to determine your personal interests. These surveys are strictly voluntary. The data collected through these surveys will be used solely to determine the type of advertisements you will be exposed with when you are logged in to your control panel account. Each survey will be sponsored by our partners, which will be in a form of survey prizes. However, any PII collected will not be shared in any way to any of our partners or affiliates. The information collected will only be used to enhance our Web site and your experience and to award prizes. The surveys will be prompted when you are logging in to your FreeHostingCloud.com account, a new survey will be prompted to you, whenever it is available. 

**Communications From The Site**

When we receive email, we use return email addresses to reply with the information requested. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. When supplying contact information to FreeHostingCloud.com you can indicate your preference if you would like to be contacted to receive information and updates about our services by logging in to your FreeHostingCloud.com account, going to your member profile page and choose not to receive any further notification emails from us or other information pertaining to FreeHostingCloud.com. Information you submit to us will not be used for this purpose unless you indicate this as your preference. When supplying contact information to FreeHostingCloud.com you can indicate your preference on your members profile page to participate in the FreeHostingCloud.com program if you would like to receive special offers from other companies that we think may be of interest to you through our periodically newsletter. Information you submit to us will not be used for this purpose unless you elect to participate in the FreeHostingCloud.com program or otherwise consent. You will receive a confirmation email from us when placing an order on our site and paying through one of our trusted 3rd parties such as PayPal or GoogleCheckout. They only share back information with us about the transaction such as your name, item ordered, email address, etc. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you register for our free services, but choose not to receive any promotional newsletter concerning our updated services. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at privacy@FreeHostingCloud.com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our member profile page, or you may contact us at privacy@FreeHostingCloud.com or to FreeHostingCloud.com ADDRESS to opt-out. You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. Generally, you may not opt-out of service related communications (such as replying to your emails, order confirmation emails, etc.) which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by contacting us at privacy@FreeHostingCloud.com. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and services, and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our Web site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women use a certain service, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals unless they indicated this as their preference by participating in the FreeHostingCloud.com program. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

**Personally identifiable information:**

FreeHostingCloud.com does not share, sell, rent, or trade PII with third parties for their promotional purposes except with your consent as described in this privacy policy Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described within this privacy policy without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your password-protected account and selecting to update your Profile or Personal Info. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Specific Terms and Conditions**

FreeHostingCloud.com considers email transmitted via our service to be the private correspondence between the sender and recipient. We will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of a user`s private communications, except as required by law, to comply with legal process, if necessary to enforce the Service Agreement, to respond to claims that such contents violate the rights of third-parties, or to protect the rights or property of FreeHostingCloud.com. By using the service you agree that technical processing of email communications is and may be required to send and receive messages, to conform to the technical requirements of connecting networks, to conform to the limitations of the Service, or to conform to other, similar technical requirements. By using the service you acknowledge and agree that FreeHostingCloud.com do not endorse the content of any user communications and are not responsible or liable for any unlawful, harassing, libelous, privacy invading, abusive, threatening, harmful, vulgar, obscene, tortuous, or otherwise objectionable content, or content that infringes or may infringe the intellectual property or other rights of another. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at privacy@FreeHostingCloud.com 

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by FreeHostingCloud.com. Please be aware that we, FreeHostingCloud.com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
